Guide to the Columbia Unoversity Press Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Arranged Files
  - Greena - Greenb (Box 87)
  - Greene, Evarts Boutell, Virginia D. Harrington, & Richard Brandon Morris (Box 87)
  - Greene, Lorenzo Johnston (Box 87)
  - Greene (Box 87)
  - Greeni - Greens (Box 88)
  - Greenough, William Croan (Box 88)
  - Greenwood (Box 88)
  - Greenwood, Ernest (Box 88)
  - Greet, William Cabell & Allen Walker Read (Box 88)
  - Greg - Greu (Box 88)
  - Gregory, William King et al. (Box 88)
  - Greig, Gertrud Berta (Box 88)
  - Grennan, Margaret Rose (Box 88)
  - Grey, Lennox (Box 88)
  - Gria - Grif (Box 89)
  - Grier, Elizabeth (Box 89)
  - Grierson, Sir Herbert John Clifford (Box 89)
  - Gries, Konrad (Box 89)
  - Griffin, Charles Carroll (Box 89)
  - Griffith, Ernest Stacey (Box 89)
  - Grig - Gris (Box 89)
  - Groce, George Cuthbert (Box 89)
  - Grod - Gros (Box 89)
  - Groethuysen, Bernhard (Box 89)
  - Groot, Gerard J. & Bertram S. Kraus (Box 89)
  - Gross (Box 89)
  - Gross, Feliks (Box 89)
  - Grossman, Kurt R. (Box 89)
  - Grot - Gru (Box 90)
  - Grout, Donald Jay (Box 90)
  - Grubb, Gerald G. (Box 90)
  - Grunebaum, Gustave E. von & Mead Abel (Box 90)
  - Grunfel, Judith (Box 90)
  - Grutzmacher, Richard H. (Box 90)
  - Gu - Gun (Box 90)
  - Guild, June Purcell (Box 90)
  - Gur - Gw (Box 90)
  - Gusti, Dimitrie (Box 90)
  - Guthrie, William Dameron (Box 90)
  - Guttman, Selma (Box 90)
  - Haa - Hab (Box 90)
  - Haas, William S. (Box 90)
  - Haase, Gladys D. (Box 90)
  - Haberler, Gottfried (Box 90)
  - Hac - Hag (Box 91)
  - Hacker, Louis Morton (Box 91)
  - Hadas, Moses & Merriam M. Sherwood (Box 91)
  - Hahn (Box 91)
  - Haig, Robert Murray & Cark Sumner Shoup (Box 91)
  - Haik - Hain (Box 92)
  - Haines, Helen Elizabeth (Box 92)
  - Hal - Halj (Box 93)
  - Halbwachs, Maurice (Box 93)
  - Hale, Robert Lee (Box 93)
  - Hall (Box 93)
  - Hall, Charles Swain (Box 93)
  - Hall, Courtney Robert (Box 93)
  - Hall, Edward Twitchell (Box 93)
  - Hall, Henry Marion (Box 93)
  - Hall, Vernon (Box 93)
  - Hall (Box 93)
  - Haller, William (1885- ) & Godfrey Davies (Box 93)
  - Haller, William (1914- ) (Box 93)
  - Hallett, Harold Foster (Box 93)
  - Halp - Hals (Box 94)
  - Ham - Hamb (Box 94)
  - Hamilton (Box 94)
  - Hamilton, George Livingstone (Box 94)
  - Hamiltom, Gordon (Box 94)
  - Hamilton, Milton Wheaton (Box 94)
  - Hamilton, Walton Hale (Box 94)
  - Hamlin, Genevieve Karr (Box 95)
  - Hamlin, Talbot Faulkner & Leopold Arnaud (Box 95)
  - Hamm - Hamu (Box 95)
  - Hammer, Jacob (Box 95)
  - Hammerschmidt, William W. (Box 95)
  - Hammond, William Gardiner (Box 95)
  - Hampton (Box 95)
  - Hanc - Hann (Box 96)
  - Handbook of American Indian languages (Box 96)
  - Handbook of Latin American studies (Box 96)
  - Hans (Box 96)
  - Hansen; Hanson (Box 96)
  - Hansen, Ida Miller (Box 96)
  - Hantz, Harold D. (Box 96)
  - Hara - Han (Box 96)
  - Harbage, Alfred (Box 96)
  - Harbers, Henry J. (Box 96)
  - Hardy, Edward Rochie (Box 96)
  - Hare, Richard Gilbert (Box 96)
  - Haring, Douglas Gilbert (Box 96)
  - Harkins, William Edward, Marie Hnyková, Clarence A. Manning & Klement Simoncic (Box 96)
  - Harl - Harp (Box 96)
  - Harlan, Aurelia Brooks (Box 96)
  - Harley, Lewis Riefsneider (Box 96)
  - Harms, Ernst (Box 96)
  - Harper, Lawrence Averell (Box 96)
  - Harr (Box 97)
  - Harrington, Virginia Draper (Box 97)
  - Harris; Harrison (Box 97)
  - Harris, Frederick Philip (Box 97)
  - Harrison, John Smith (Box 97)
  - Hart (Box 97)
  - Hartley, Eugene Leonard (Box 97)
  - Hartley, Ruth Edith (Box 97)
  - Hantman (n) (Box 97)
  - Hartmann, Edward George (Box 97)
  - Hartmann, Jacob Wittmer (Box 97)
  - Hartw - Harw (Box 97)
  - Has (Box 97)
  - Haskell, Juliana Catherine Shields (Box 97)
  - Hat - Hav (Box 97)
  - Hatfield, Charles William (Box 97)
  - Hatfield, Henry Caraway (Box 97)
  - Hathaway, Winifred Phillips (Box 97)
  - Hauch, Edward Franklin (Box 97)
  - Haw (Box 98)
  - Hawley, Charles Arthur (Box 98)
  - Hawley, Paul Ramsey (Box 98)
  - Hay - Haz (Box 98)
  - Hayden (Box 98)
  - Hayes; Hays (Box 98)
  - Hayes, Carlton Joseph Huntley (Box 98)
  - Hayes,William Henry (Box 98)
  - Heywood, Charles (Box 98)
  - Hazzard, Florence Woolsey (Box 98)
  - Hea - Heb (Box 98)
  - Heatwole, Oliver W. (Box 98)
  - Hebel, John William, F. A. Patterson, & CM M. Coffin (Box 98)
  - Hec - Hee (Box 98)
  - Heck, Earl L. W. (Box 98)
  - Hecker, Julius F. (Box 98)
  - Hei (Box 98)
  - Heidel, WIlliam Arthur (Box 98)
  - Heinrich, H. W. (Box 98)
  - Hel - Hem (Box 98)
  - Hemminghaus, Edgar Hugo (Box 98)
  - Hen - Henk (Box 99)
  - Hendel, Samuel (Box 99)
  - Henderson (Box 99)
  - Henderson, Harold G. (Box 99)
  - Hendricks, Luther Virgil (Box 99)
  - Henig, Harry (Box 99)
  - Henn - Hep (Box 99)
  - Henricks, Namee (Mrs Walter A.) (Box 99)
  - Henry (Box 99)
  - Herb - Hern (Box 99)
  - Herne, Julie A & Herbert Edwards (Box 99)
  - Herold, Amos Lee (Box 99)
  - Herold, Jean Christopher (Box 99)
  - Herr - Herz (Box 99)
  - Heskovits, Melville Jean (Box 99)
  - Hertz, David Bendel (Box 99)
  - Hes - Het (Box 100)
  - Heu-Hey (Box 100)
  - Hewes, Amy (Box 100)
  - Hib-Hie (Box 100)
  - Hicks, James R. (Box 100)
  - Hieatt, A. Kent (Box 100)
  - Hig-Hij (Box 100)
  - Higginson, James Jackson (Box 100)
  - Hila - Hild (Box 100)
  - Hildreth, Gertrude Powell (Box 100)
  - Hill (Box 100)
  - Hill, Frank Ernest & W.E Williams (Box 100)
  - Hill, Robert Tudor (Box 100)
  - Hille - Him (Box 100)
  - Hillebrand, Harold Newcornb (Box 100)
  - Hillenbrand, Martin Joseph (Box 100)
  - Hilliard, Albert Leroy (Box 100)
  - Hin - Hio (Box 101)
  - Hindus, Milton (Box 101)
  - Hinkhouse, Fred Junkin (Box 101)
  - Hinsie, Leland Earl (Box 101)
  - Hir - His (Box 101)
  - Hirsch, Felix Edward (Box 101)
  - Hishida Seiji George (Box 101)
  - History, etc. (Box 101)
  - Hit (Box 101)
  - Hitti, Philip Khuri (Box 101)
  - Ho - Hoc (Box 101)
  - Hoadland, Marjorie (Box 101)
  - Hobhouse, Leonard Trelawney (Box 101)
  - Hod - Hoe (Box 101)
  - Hof (Box 101)
  - Hoffman, Harold Leroy (Box 101)
  - Hofstadter, Richard & C. De Witt Hardy (Box 101)
  - Hog - Hoh (Box 102)
  - Hogan, Michael John (Box 102)
  - Hoijer, Harry (Box 102)
  - Hok, Ruth Eunice Carter (Box 102)
  - Holb - Holli (Box 102)
  - Holbrook, Richard Thayer (Box 102)
  - Holdsworth, William Searles (Box 102)
  - Hollander, Lee Milton (Box 102)
  - Holleran, Mary Patricia (Box 102)
  - Hollingworth, Harry L. (Box 102)
  - Hollinshead, Byron Sharpe (Box 102)
  - Hollis, Ernest Victor & Alice L. Taylor (Box 102)
  - Hollister, William Wallace (Box 102)
  - Hollm - Holly (Box 103)
  - Holloway, Emory & Vernolian Schwarz (Box 103)
  - Holman (Box 103)
  - Holmes (Box 103)
  - Holmes, Henry A. (Box 103)
  - Holt - Hom (Box 103)
  - Holtzman, Estelle Filia (Box 103)
  - Holzman, Robert S. (Box 103)
  - Hon - Hop (Box 103)
  - Hooker, Kenneth Ward (Box 103)
  - Hoover, Merle Montgomery (Box 103)
  - Hope, Richard (Box 103)
  - Hopkins, Arthur John (Box 103)
  - Hopper, Vincent Foster (Box 103)
  - Hor (Box 104)
  - Hornaday, Clifford Lee (Box 104)
  - Horsfall, Frank Lappin (Box 104)
  - Horwood, Murray P. (Box 104)
  - Hos - Hot (Box 104)
  - Hou - Hov (Box 104)
  - Houk, Raymond Aaron (Box 104)
  - House, Albert Virgil (Box 104)
  - Houtchens, Lawrence Huston & Carolyn Washburn Houtchens (Box 104)
  - How - Howa (Box 104)
  - Howard (Box 104)
  - Howard, Arthur David (Box 104)
  - Howard, Clare M. (Box 104)
  - Howe (Box 105)
  - Howe, Herbert Barber (Box 105)
  - Howe, Susanne (Mrs George Nobbe) (Box 105)
  - Howe, Winifred Eva (Box 105)
  - Howel - Hs (Box 105)
  - Howson, Roger (Box 105)
  - Hsu, Francis Lang-kwang (Box 105)
  - Hu, Shih (Box 105)
  - Hubbell, Allan Forbes (Box 105)
  - Hubert, Merton Jerome & John L. La Monte (Box 105)
  - Hudson; Hu - Hud (Box 105)
  - Hue - Hug (Box 105)
  - Hufeland, Otto (Box 105)
  - Hughes (Box 105)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans (Box 105)
  - Hughes, Charles H. (Box 105)
  - Hughley, Judge Neal (Box 105)
  - Hul - Hum (Box 106)
  - Hun - Hur (Box 106)
  - The Hungarian Quarterly (Box 106)
  - Hungerford, Edward Buell (Box 106)
  - Hunt, Alice Riggs (Box 106)
  - Hunt, Mary Leland (Box 106)
  - Hunter (Box 106)
  - Hunter, Floyd, Cecil G. Sheps, & Ruth M. Connor (Box 106)
  - Hunter, Louis C. (Box 106)
  - Huntley, Kate Eleanor (Box 106)
  - Hurwitz, Samuel Justin (Box 106)
  - Hus - Hw (Box 106)
  - Hutchinson, Dorothy Carleton Hewitt (Box 106)
  - Hutsel, Eleonore Louise (Box 106)
  - Hy. (Box 107)
  - Hyde (Box 107)
  - Hyde, Mary Morley Crapo (Box 107)
  - Hyde, Albert Woodburn (Box 107)
  - Hypes, James Lowell (Box 107)
  - Hyslop, Beatrice Fry (Box 107)
  - Hytier, Jean (Box 107)
  - Ia - Im (Box 107)
  - Ihrig, Grace Pauline (Box 107)
  - Ilbert, Sir Courtenay Peregrine (Box 107)
  - In - Ins (Box 107)
  - The Index Society (Box 107)
  - Ingrain, Tolbert R. (Box 107)
  - Int -Io (Box 108)
  - International Congress on Mental Health (Box 108)
  - International Documents Service (Box 108)
  - International Economic Relations of the U.S.Series (Box 108)
  - International Institute of Social Research (Box 108)
  - International Journal of American Linguistics (Box 108)
  - International Monetary Fund (Box 108)
  - International Society for Literature and Arts (Box 108)
  - Ion, Theodore P. (Box 108)
  - Iowa Lecture Series (Box 108)
  - Ira - Irv (Box 108)
  - Irwin (Box 109)
  - Irwin, Ray W. & Edna L. Jacobsen (Box 109)
  - Irwin, William Robert (Box 109)
  - Is-Iv (Box 109)
  - Ise, John (Box 109)
  - Izard, Thomas Clarence (Box 109)
  - Jack (Box 110)
  - Jackson (Box 110)
  - Jackson, Abraham Valentine Williams (Box 110)
  - Jackson, Robert Houghwout (Box 110)
  - Jacob[s], [Y] (Box 110)
  - Jacob, Cary Franklin (Box 110)
  - Jacobs, Melville (Box 110)
  - Jacobi - Jad (Box 110)
  - Jacoby, Erich Hellmuth (Box 110)
  - Jacoby, Sidney B. (Box 110)
  - Jaffe, Raymond & John W. Yolton (Box 110)
  - Jag - Jam (Box 110)
  - James (Box 110)
  - Jam[i]eson (Box 110)
  - Jameson, Elsa Denison (Box 110)
  - Jamieson, John (Box 110)
  - Jan - Jas (Box 111)
  - Janowsky, Oscar I (Box 111)
  - Jarrett, Mary Cromwell (Box 111)
  - Jasny, Naum (Box 111)
  - Jea - Jel (Box 111)
  - Jeffreys (Box 111)
  - Jelliffe, Robert A. (Box 111)
  - Jenkins[on] (Box 111)
  - Jenks, Jeremiah W. (Box 111)
  - Jenks, William Alexander (Box 111)
  - Jennings (Box 111)
  - Jennings, E. Allen (Box 111)
  - Jennings, Herbert Spencer (Box 111)
  - Jennings, Pauline (Box 111)
  - Jensen, Gerard E. (Box 111)
  - Jer - Jh (Box 111)
  - Jessup, Philip Caryl; Francis Deak; W. Alison Phillips; Arthur H. Reede; & Edgar G. Turlington (Box 111)
  - Jewett, Ida A. & Hyman Eigerman (Box 111)
  - Joa - Joe (Box 112)
  - Joad, Cyril Edwin Mitchinson (Box 112)
  - Job, Leonard Bliss (Box 112)
  - Joh. (Box 112)
  - John, Lisle Cecil (Box 112)
  - Johnson (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Claudius O. (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Douglas Wilson (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Geoffrey (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Harold Earle (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Henry (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Howard (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Isabel S. (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Louise H. (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Martin Christopher (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Samuel, 1696-1772 (Box 112)
  - Johnson, Samuel. 1709-1784 (Box 112)
  - Johnston, George Burke (Box 113)
  - Jol. (Box 113)
  - Jon (Box 113)
  - Jonas, Leah (Box 113)
  - Jones (Box 113)
  - Jones, David E. (Box 113)
  - Jones, Howard P. (Box 113)
  - Jones, Leslie Webber (Box 113)
  - Jones, Louis Clark (Box 113)
  - Jones, Richard Foster (Box 113)
  - Jordan (Box 113)
  - Jordan, Elijah (Box 113)
  - Jos (Box 113)
  - Jourde, Paul C (Box 114)
  - Journal... (Box 114)
  - Journal of Geomorphology (Box 114)
  - Journal of Psychiatric Social Work (Box 114)
  - Journalism (Box 114)
  - Joy (Box 114)
  - Ju (Box 114)
  - July, Edythe Norton (Box 114)
  - Jurgela, Constantine R. (Box 114)
  - Ka - Kak (Box 115)
  - Kagan, Henry Enoch (Box 115)
  - Kahn, Alfred Edward (Box 115)
  - Kahn, Alfred J. (Box 115)
  - Kahn, Ludwig W. (Box 115)
  - Kahn, Sholom Jacob (Box 115)
  - Kal. (Box 115)
  - Kalcik, Vaclav V. (Box 115)
  - Kallay, Miklos (Box 115)
  - Kallen, Horace Meyer (Box 115)
  - Kallmann, Franz J. (Box 115)
  - Kaltchas, Nicholas Stavrou (Box 115)
  - Kam - Kao (Box 116)
  - Kann, Robert A. (Box 116)
  - Kant, Immanuel (Box 116)
  - Kap - Kara (Box 116)
  - Kaplan (Box 116)
  - Kaplan, Estelle (Box 116)
  - Kaplan, Max (Box 116)
  - Kaplan, Milton Allen (Box 116)
  - Kapp, Ernst (Box 116)
  - Kapp, K. William (Box 116)
  - Karamzin, Nikolai Mikhailovich (Box 116)
  - Kardiner, Abram (Box 117)
  - Karel, Leonard & Elizabeth Spencer Roach (Box 117)
  - Karelitz, George & Ormondroyd, J. (Box 117)
  - Karf - Karz (Box 117)
  - Karolyi, Alexander F. (Box 117)
  - Karpf, Maurice J. (Box 117)
  - Karpman, Benjamin (Box 117)
  - Karson, Irwin Marc (Box 117)
  - Kas - Kc (Box 118)
  - Katibah, H. I. (Box 118)
  - Katona, George (Box 118)
  - Katz, Blanche (Box 118)
  - Katz, Joseph (Box 118)
  - Katz, Mordecai (Box 118)
  - Kaufmann, F. W. (Box 118)
  - Kea (Box 118)
  - Kee - Kei (Box 118)
  - Keil, Gunther (Box 118)
  - Keller, Arthur Schopenhauer, Oliver J. Lissitzyn, & Frederick J. Mann (Box 118)
  - Kell (Box 118)
  - Kelley; Kelly (Box 118)
  - Kelley, Douglas M. (Box 118)
  - Kelly, John Frederick (Box 118)
  - Kelm - Kem (Box 118)
  - Kemp, James Furman (Box 118)
  - Kendall (Box 119)
  - Kenn - Kep (Box 119)
  - Kennedy, Louise Venable (Box 119)
  - Kennedy, Van Dusen (Box 119)
  - Kennedy, William Francis (Box 119)
  - Kenney, James Francis (Box 119)
  - Kent, Donald Peterson (Box 119)
  - Kenyon, John S. (Box 119)
  - Kepple, David (Box 119)
  - Kepple, Frederick Paul (Box 119)
  - Ker (Box 119)
  - Kerr (Box 119)
  - Kes - Key (Box 119)
  - Kessler, Henry Howard (Box 119)
  - Kester, Roy B. & Howell A. Inghram (Box 119)
  - Keyes, Clinton W. & George N. Olcott (Box 120)
  - Keys, Alice Mapelsden (Box 120)
  - Keyser, Cassius Jackson (Box 120)
  - Kh (Box 120)
  - Kiang, Wen-Han (Box 120)
  - Kibre, Pearl (Box 120)
  - Kid - Kih (Box 120)
  - Kidd, John Graydon (Box 120)
  - Kim (Box 120)
  - Kind (Box 120)
  - Kindleberger, Charles Poor (Box 120)
  - King - Kint (Box 121)
  - King, Joseph Leonard (Box 121)
  - Kingdon, Robert M. (Box 121)
  - Kingsbury, Laura Mabel (Box 121)
  - Kinne, Willard Austin (Box 121)
  - Kipnis, Ira (Box 121)
  - Kir - Kj (Box 121)
  - Kirchner, Walther (Box 121)
  - Kirk, Grayson Louis (Box 121)
  - Kirk, Rudolf See also: English Institute (Box 121)
  - Kirkman, Francis (Box 121)
  - Kjellatrom, Erik Torsten Hjalmar (Box 121)
  - Kla - Kle (Box 122)
  - Kleffens, Eelco Nicholaas van (Box 122)
  - Klein, Anita E. (Mrs. Clarence Young) (Box 122)
  - Klein, Philip & Ruth Voris (Box 122)
  - Ku - Klu (Box 122)
  - Klineberg, Otto (Box 122)
  - Kna - Kni (Box 123)
  - Knapp, Charles (Box 123)
  - Knappen, Laurence Stevens (Box 123)
  - Knapton, Ernest John (Box 123)
  - Kneller, George Frederick (Box 123)
  - Kno - Knu (Box 123)
  - Knox Israel (Box 123)
  - Knox, Raymond Collyer (Box 123)
  - Kob - Kog (Box 123)
  - Koch, Adrienne (Box 123)
  - Koch, G. Adolf (Box 123)
  - Koenig, Louis William (Box 123)
  - Koeves, Tibor (Box 123)
  - Koh - Kol (Box 124)
  - Kohn, Hans (Box 124)
  - Koht, Halvdan & Sigmund Skard (Box 124)
  - Kon - Kop (Box 124)
  - Konkle, Burton Alva (Box 124)
  - Konvitz, Milton Ridvas (Box 124)
  - Koo, Vi Kyuin Wellington (Box 124)
  - Koo, Wellington, Jr (Box 124)
  - Koos, Earl Lomon (Box 124)
  - Kor (Box 125)
  - Korte, Alfred, Moses Hadas, & Jacob Hammer (Box 125)
  - Kos - Koz (Box 125)
  - Kosary, Dominic G. (Box 125)
  - Koyre, Alexandre & Leonora Cohen Rosenfield (Box 125)
  - Krab - Kram (Box 125)
  - Kraeling, Carl Hermann (Box 125)
  - Kraeling, Emil Gottlieb Heinrich & Janet R. Aiken (Box 125)
  - Kramer, Stella (Box 125)
  - Kran (Box 125)
  - Krap - Krau (Box 126)
  - Krapp, George Philip (Box 126)
  - Kre (Box 126)
  - Kreisberg, Adolph (Box 126)
  - Kramer, J. Bruce (Box 126)
  - Kri (Box 126)
  - Kridl, Manfred (Box 126)
  - Krikorian, Yervant Hovhannes (Box 126)
  - Kristeller, Paul Oskar (Box 126)
  - Kro (Box 127)
  - Krows, Marion Soetemon (Mrs Arthur Edwin) (Box 127)
  - Kru-Krz (Box 127)
  - Krueger, Leonard (Box 127)
  - Kruger, Fritz-Konrad (Box 127)
  - Krutch, Joseph Wood (Box 127)
  - Kub - Kuh (Box 127)
  - Kuhn, Alvin B. (Box 127)
  - Kul - Kup (Box 127)
  - Kulischer, Eugene Michel (Box 127)
  - Kunitz, Joshua (Box 127)
  - Kunkel, Fred E. (Box 127)
  - Kur - Ky (Box 128)
  - Kurtz, Dorothy L. (Box 128)
  - Kybal, Vlastimil (Box 128)
  - Kurz, Harry (Box 128)
  - Lab - Lad (Box 128)
  - Lachmann, Kurt (Box 128)
  - Laf - Lal (Box 128)
  - Laird, John (Box 128)
  - Lam (Box 128)
  - Lamarque, Ernest C. W. (Box 128)
  - La Meri, Mme (Box 128)
  - Lamont, William Dawson (Box 128)
  - La Monte, John L. & Merton Jerome Hubert (Box 128)
  - Lamprecht, Sterling Power (Box 128)
  - Lancaster, Charles Maxwell (Box 128)
  - Land (Box 128)
  - Landes, Ruth (Box 128)
  - Landheer, Bartholomew (Box 128)
  - Landis, Benson Young (Box 128)
  - Lane, William G. (Box 129)
  - Lang - Lange (Box 129)
  - Langdale, Abram Barnett (Box 129)
  - Langn - Lany (Box 129)
  - Langsam, Gert Geoffrey (Box 129)
  - Langstaff, John Brett (Box 129)
  - Lans, Asher B. (Box 129)
  - Lanux, Pierre de (Box 129)
  - Lanz, Henry (Box 129)
  - Lar (Box 129)
  - Larguier, Everett H. (Box 129)
  - Larkin, John Day (Box 129)
  - Larkin, Sarah (Box 129)
  - Larrabee, Stephen Addison (Box 129)
  - Larson, Harold (Box 129)
  - Larson, Laurence M. (Box 129)
  - Las (Box 129)
  - Laserson, Max M & James Thomson Shotwell (Box 129)
  - Lat (Box 130)
  - Latham, Minor Waite (Box 130)
  - Lau - Lav (Box 130)
  - Lau, Robert Julius (Box 130)
  - Lauterbach, Albert T (Box 130)
  - Lauterpacht, Hersch (Box 130)
  - Law - Lawn (Box 130)
  - Lawley, F.E. (Box 130)
  - Lawrence (Box 130)
  - Lawrence, William Witherle (Box 130)
  - Lawton, George (Box 131)
  - Lay (Box 132)
  - Lazarsfeld, Paul Felix; Bernard Berelson; Hazel Gaudet; Particia, Kendall; & Mirra Komarovsky (Box 132)
  - Lea - Lee (Box 132)
  - Leary, Lewis Gaston (Box 132)
  - Leavitt, John Anton (Box 132)
  - Le Boutillier, Cornelia Geer (Box 132)
  - Le Comte, Edward Semple (Box 132)
  - Le Coq, John P. (Box 132)
  - Led - Leeu (Box 132)
  - Le Due, Thomas Harold Andre (Box 132)
  - Lee (Box 132)
  - Lee, Grace Chin (Box 132)
  - Lee, Maurice de Pont (Box 132)
  - Lee, Porter Raymond (Box 132)
  - Leerburger, Franklin J. (Box 132)
  - Lef - Leh (Box 133)
  - Lehmann-Haupt, Hellmut (Box 133)
  - Lei - Lem (Box 133)
  - Leigh, Robert Devore (Box 133)
  - Leishman, James B. (Box 133)
  - Leisy, Ernest E. (Box 133)
  - Leiter, Robert David (Box 133)
  - Lemont, Jessie (Box 133)
  - Len - Leo (Box 133)
  - Lent, George Eidt (Box 133)
  - Leonard, William Norris (Box 133)
  - Lepley, Ray (Box 134)
  - Ler - Leu (Box 134)
  - Lesser, Alexander (Box 134)
  - Letiche, John M. (Box 134)
  - Leuchs, Fritz Adolphe Herman (Box 134)
  - Levandis, John Alexander (Box 134)
  - Leve. (Box 134)
  - Levi (Box 134)
  - Levine, David (Box 134)
  - Levy (Box 134)
  - Levy, Babette May (Box 134)
  - Levy, Beryl Harold (Box 134)
  - Levy, David Mordecai (Box 134)
  - Levy, S. leon (Box 134)
  - Lew - Ley (Box 134)
  - Lewinson, Thea Stein & Joseph Zubin (Box 134)
  - Lewis (Box 134)
  - Lewis, Claudia Louise (Box 134)
  - Lewis, John (Box 134)
  - Lewis, Naphtali & Meyer Reinhold (Box 134)
  - Lewton, Elizabeth & Edna Gersh (Box 135)
  - Levy, Immanuel (Box 135)
  - Li - Lie (Box 135)
  - Lichtwitz, Leopold (Box 135)
  - Lie - Lil (Box 135)
  - Liedke, Herbert R (Box 135)
  - Lief, Alfred (Box 135)
  - Lightbourn, James H. (Box 135)
  - Linc - Lind (Box 135)
  - Lindberg, John (Box 135)
  - Lindsay, Frank Whiteman (Box 135)
  - Lindsay, Vachel Records (Box 135)
  - Line - Ling (Box 135)
  - Lindsley, James E. (Box 135)
  - Link, Edith Murr (Box 135)
  - Link, Eugene Perry (Box 135)
  - Lint - Lip (Box 136)
  - Linton, Ralph (Box 136)
  - Lipkind, William (Box 136)
  - Liptzin, Solomon (Box 136)
  - Lis - Li (Box 136)
  - Little, Alan MacNaughton Gordon (Box 136)
  - Liu, Bangnee Alfred (Box 136)
  - Livingston, Arthur (Box 136)
  - Lo - Lod (Box 137)
  - Lobeck, Armin Kohl (Box 137)
  - Lobel, Paul A. (Box 137)
  - Lockwood, Helen Drusilla (Box 137)
  - Loe - Lom (Box 137)
  - Loggins, Vernon (Box 137)
  - Loiseau, Louis Auguste (Box 137)
  - Lan - Lop (Box 137)
  - Loomis, Roger Sherman (Box 137)
  - Lor - Lot (Box 138)
  - Lord, Clifford Lee (Box 138)
  - Lorenz, Theodore (Box 138)
  - Losey, Mary (Box 138)
  - Loshe, Lillie Deming (Box 138)
  - Lott, George M. (Box 138)
  - Lottman, Herbert R. (Box 138)
  - Lou - Lov (Box 138)
  - Loucks, Emerson H. (Box 138)
  - Loughrey, Mary Ellen (Box 138)
  - Lovell, Laura H. (Box 138)
  - Low - Lowe (Box 138)
  - Lowenstein-Wertheim-Freudenberg, Hubertus, Prinz zu (Box 138)
  - Lowenstein, Milton Dewey (Box 138)
  - Lowinger, Armand (Box 138)
  - Lowinsky, Edward Elias (Box 138)
  - Lown - Lowr (Box 139)
  - Lowrey, Lawson Gentry (Box 139)
  - Lowry, Fern (Box 139)
  - Loy, John Robert (Box 139)
  - Lub - Lud (Box 139)
  - Luck, Alma Maria (Box 139)
  - Lucke, Charles Edward (Box 139)
  - Ludlum, David McWilliams (Box 139)
  - Luhrs, Marie (Box 139)
  - Luk - Lun (Box 140)
  - Luker, Benjamin Franklin (Box 140)
  - Lundberg, George Andrew, Mirra Komarovsky, & Mary Alice McInerny (Box 140)
  - Lunt, William Edward (Box 140)
  - Luq - Lut (Box 140)
  - Luria, Salvador E. (Box 140)
  - Lurie, Samuel (Box 140)
  - Lya - Lyn (Box 140)
  - Lynch, David (Box 140)
  - Lynd, Helen Merrell (Box 140)
  - Lyo (Box 140)
  - Lyon, John Henry Hobart (Box 140)
  - Lyseuko, Trofim Denisovich & Theodosius Dobzhansky (Box 140)
  - Maas, Henry S. (Box 140)
  - Mabbott, Thomas Ollive (Box 140)
  - Mabee, Carleton (Box 140)
  - MacA. (Box 141)
  - McAvoy, Thomas Timothy (Box 141)
  - McBain, Howard Lee (Box 141)
  - McCab - McCan (Box 141)
  - McCamy, James Lucian (Box 141)
  - McCann, Franklin Thresher (Box 141)
  - McCar - McCh (Box 141)
  - McCarthy, John Willadams (Box 141)
  - McCl (Box 141)
  - McClure, Wallace Mitchell (Box 141)
  - McCo (Box 141)
  - McCormick, Mary Josephine (Box 141)
  - McCr - McCu (Box 141)
  - McCrea, Nelson Glenn (Box 141)
  - McCrea, Roswell Cheney (Box 141)
  - McD (Box 141)
  - McE - McF (Box 141)
  - McEuen, Kathryn Anderson (Box 141)
  - McFarland, Charles S. (Box 141)
  - McGa - McGo (Box 142)
  - McGinley, James Joseph (Box 142)
  - McGoldrick, Joseph Daniel (Box 142)
  - McGr (Box 142)
  - McGraw, Myrtle Byram (Box 142)
  - McH - McJ (Box 142)
  - Maclver, Robert Morrison (Box 142)
  - McJimsey, George Davis (Box 142)
  - Mack, Edward Clarence (Box 143)
  - Mack, Ruth Prince (Box 143)
  - McK (Box 143)
  - McKay, George Leslie (Box 143)
  - MacKay, Kenneth Campbell (Box 143)
  - McKean, Dayton David (Box 143)
  - McKee, Samuel (Box 143)
  - McKeon, Charles King (Box 143)
  - McKeon, Richard P. (Box 143)
  - McL (Box 143)
  - MacLeod, Colin Munro (Box 143)
  - McM (Box 143)
  - Macmahon, Arthur Whittier & John D. Millett (Box 143)
  - McN (Box 144)
  - McNair, Arnold Duncan McNair, Baron (Box 144)
  - MacNair, Everett W. (Box 144)
  - McNaughton, Wayne L. (Box 144)
  - McNeal, Edgar Holmes (Box 144)
  - McNeill, John Thomas & Helena M. Gamer (Box 144)
  - McP - McW (Box 144)
  - McPherson, T. F. (Box 144)
  - Macrorie, Ken (Box 144)
  - Macurdy, Grace Harriet (Box 144)
  - Macy, Josiah, Jr. Foundation (Box 144)
  - Mad (Box 144)
  - Maerz, A. (Box 144)
  - Mag (Box 144)
  - Magid English Political Pluralism, 1941 (Box 144)
  - Mah - Mak (Box 144)
  - Maier, Josef (Box 144)
  - Mal - Mall (Box 144)
  - Malm - Maly (Box 144)
  - Malone, Kemp (Box 144)
  - Megill, Roswell The Impact of Federal Taxes (Box 144)
  - Manc - Manl (Box 145)